Guide to the Ellen Van Volkenburg and Maurice Browne papers vvb
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- Writings
  - Maurice Browne writings
    - Maurice Browne miscellaneous writings
      - Maurice Browne drama criticism (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne essays (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne lecture materials (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne lectures (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne literary criticism and reviews (Box 16)
      - London Theatre articles (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne manuscript articles (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 16)
        Includes fragments. Various dates and undated items.
      - Manuscripts of BBC talks (Box 16)
      - "Memorandum on the Need for Advanced Training of Directors of Acting...", 1949 (Box 16)
      - Nativity Play (Box 16)
        Preliminary draft.
      - "Notices of Early Book by Maurice Browne" clippings, 1905 (Box 16)
      - Philosophy and Aesthetics (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne political articles (Box 16)
      - Maurice Browne reading lists (Box 16)
      - Items removed from Maurice Browne's letters to Ellen Van Volkenburg (Box 16)
      - The Repertory Company's Seattle Season (Box 16)
      - The Scribe (Box 16)
      - Theatre Associations (Box 16)
      - Theatrical Confession (Box 16)
  - Ellen Van Volkenburg writings
    - Ellen Van Volkenburg plays
      - Ameriga Vespucci: A Play in Three Acts
        Written under the pseudonym "Emily Hoyt".
        - Ameriga Vespucci draft, 138 Leaves (Box 16)
          Includes a 108-leaf draft and 30 leaves of notes and ideas.
        - Ameriga Vespucci drafts, clippings, and correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescript (Box 16)
          Carbon copy with holograph revisions. "Copyrighted (under name 'Emily Hoyt')." Title page inscribed with Ellen Van Volkenburg's New York and Pasadena addresses. Accompanied by an unsigned charcoal sketch of a young woman.
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescript (Box 16)
          Carbon copy with holograph revisions. Title page inscribed with Ellen Van Volkenburg's New York address.
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescript (Box 16)
          Includes holograph revisions. "Part of original draft." Includes correspondence.
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescript (Box 16)
          Includes holograph revisions. Title page inscribed with Ellen Van Volkenburg's and Elena Miramova's addresses.
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescript (Box 16)
          Includes holograph revisions. Title page inscribed with Ellen Van Volkenburg's New York address.
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescript (Oversize 2)
        - Ameriga Vespucci typescripts, 1939 (Box 16)
          One item labeled "Working copy, Westerly, Rhode Island and Watch Hill, July 1939". Partial carbon copy with holograph revisions labeled "Original script".
        - Ameriga Vespucci materials, 1939-ca. 1955 (Box 16)
          Includes drafts, notes, and clippings.
      - The American
        Ellen Van Volkenburg's dramatization of the eponymous Henry James novel.
        - The American "Final Version" (Box 16)
          In blue folder.
        - The American photocopies, 1969 (Box 16)
          "Final draft of new pages, also discarded pages." In an envelope addressed to Mary Kennedy.
        - The American notes, 1948; 2 Volumes (Box 16)
        - The American notes, 1949 (Box 16)
          Notebook with insertions.
        - The American manuscript, December 4, 1956 (Box 16)
          Holograph. In a brown spiral notebook.
        - The American manuscript, 1957 (Box 16)
          Holograph. Each part is written in a separate notebook: Act I, Scene I; Act I, Scene II; Act II, Scene I.
        - The American typescript (Box 16)
          Carbon copy with holograph notations (underlining). In blue "Copyrighted" folder.
        - The American typescript (Box 16)
          Carbon copy with holograph revisions.
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Carbon copy with holograph revisions. In blue folder. Includes a letter from the Chichester Festival.
        - The American typescript, 1969 (Box 17)
          Carbon copy with holograph revisions. "Dennis Brown's working script, done in Barn Theatre, Darlington Hall." Accompanied by light plot and prop list.
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Mostly carbon copy, with holograph revisions. In blue folder. Accompanied by two holographs, two holograph drawings, typescript inscriptions, and a photograph.
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Mostly carbon copy, with holograph revisions. In blue folder.
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Mostly carbon copy, with holograph revisions. In brown folder inscribed "6". In manila envelope "from Zelznick Releasing Organization Inc."
        - The American typescript, ca. 1958 (Box 17)
          Includes holograph notes. One section labeled "discarded Jan./58". In manila folder labeled "The American-1906" and "To California".
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Includes holograph revisions. In black folder and black spring binder.
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Includes holograph revisions. In green folder.
        - The American typescript (Box 17)
          Includes holograph revisions. In grey folder.
        - The American typescript, ca. 1967 (Box 17)
          "Unrevised". Carbon copy with holograph revisions. In black folder.
        - The American typescript, 1949 (Box 17)
          "Working script". Carbon copy with holograph revisions. "Revised Jan 15/49". In grey-green folder.
        - The American script (Box 17)
        - The American "Items" and correspondence (Box 17)
        - The American Italian translation and Barbara Gelber materials (Box 17)
      - God and Miss Sippy notes and sketches, 1950 (Box 17)
      - The Gorgon's Head typescripts, undated; 4 folders (Box 17)
        Four annotated typescript drafts.
      - Imitative Interpretations programs and correspondence, 1910 and undated (Box 17)
      - Miss Caroline Spencer typescript, 1950 (Box 17)
        Includes holograph corrections.
      - Nine Points of the Law typescript and holograph copy, 1943? (Box 17)
      - The Queen's Keys: A Play in Three Acts
        By Madge Jenison and Ellen Van Volkenburg.
        - "Data" (Box 17)
        - "The Elizabeth Book", 1951 and undated (Box 17)
        - The Queen's Keys outline and drafts (Box 17)
        - The Queen's Keys typescript (Box 17)
          Carbon copy. In blue folder with holograph title: "Ellen Van Volkenburg's copy".
        - The Queen's Keys typescript (Box 17)
        - The Queen's Keys drafts, 1952 and undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Ellen Van Volkenburg prose
      - The Bird Cage holograph, undated (Box 17)
        "Notes...mainly for The Bird Cage."
      - Cornish manuscripts, 1956; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Genealogical notes (Box 17)
        Notes about Ellen Van Volkenburg's mother's and father's families.
      - "Nellita", 1940 and undated (Box 17)
        Two drafts.
      - "Path to Surrender", 2 folders (Box 17)
        Three drafts.
      - "Report of Fleeting Visits to Some American Community Theatres and Dramatic Schools—January to March 1929" (Box 18)
      - Theatre research and other manuscripts (Box 18)
        Includes notes for various play ideas. Various dates.
      - "Miscellaneous manuscripts removed from books", 1952-1968 and undated (Box 18)
    - Ellen Van Volkenburg miscellaneous writings, undated; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Works by Others
    - Antill, Joan
      - Antill, Joan: "Mr. Petre" (Box 18)
      - Antill, Joan: Nobody's Children film script (Box 18)
        Three drafts. "Prepared by Joan Antill."
    - Aristophanes and Davis, Blevins radio script: The Birds (Box 18)
      Adapted from the play by Aristophanes.
    - "Ballad of M. B.'s readers", undated (Box 18)
    - Barney, Alice: Do and Bedone: A Mime Ballet with a Moral (Box 18)
    - Biro, Vera poem (Box 18)
    - Brighton, Hilda: "A Quiet Sunday in the Country" (Box 18)
      Typed from published poetry?
    - Collins, Jeanne poems (Box 18)
    - Dickinson, Patric poem (Box 18)
    - Ellerbe, Alma
      - Ellerbe, Alma: "I Know a Girl" typescript (Box 18)
      - Ellerbe, Alma: "I Know a Woman" typescript (Box 18)
    - Forbes, Leon: "Kansas Tales" (Box 18)
    - Ginsbury, Norman: Viceroy Sarah, 1935 (Box 18)
      Correspondence from Maurice Browne regarding Viceroy Sarah.
    - Giovannitti, Arturo: A Pageant of Kings (Box 18)
    - Hamilton, Hugh poem (Box 18)
    - Hanline, Maurice A.: Fragments of Fears and Other Poems and Plays (Box 18)
    - Hogarth, Anne poems (Box 18)
    - Kallen, H. M. (Box 18)
    - Langer, Frantisek: Periphery, undated (Box 18)
      Translated from the Czech by Blanche Yurka and Libby Holman.
    - Ling, Barbara
      - Ling, Barbara poem (Box 18)
      - Ling, Barbara: "Apollo's Daughter" (Box 18)
    - Littell, Lydia B. poem (Box 18)
    - McGaw, Emma and Baldwin: "Travels" and "Adventure 1964" (Box 18)
    - Mounier, E. A.: Personalist Manifesto (Oversize 1)
    - Nichols, Robert
      - Nichols, Robert manuscript, undated (Box 18)
        Holograph regarding Sir Walter Raleigh.
      - Nichols, Robert correspondence (Box 18)
        Regarding Wings over Europe.
    - Nichols, Robert Malise Bowyer, and Tully, Jim: Twenty Below (Box 18)
      Includes press clippings and correspondence.
    - Obey, André: Noah (Box 18)
    - Palasovsky, Edmund: The Daughter of Jairus (Box 18)
    - Pass, H. L. (Box 18)
    - Raynal, Paul: The Unknown Warrior (Box 18)
    - Shakespeare, William: Othello
      - Sex Jealousy, or the Bore of Venice (Box 18)
        Parody of William Shakespeare's Othello.
      - Othello letters and telegrams, 1920-1930 (Box 18)
    - Urmey, Edythe Beatrice poem (Box 18)
    - Walker, Robert M.: "The Beginnings and Rise of the Organized Amateur Theater in the United States" (Box 18)
    - White, Maude Valérie musical pieces, 1897 and undated (Box 18)
      Includes "The Demon Lover" (undated) and an untitled work (1897).
    - Wolfe, Humbert: "The Fountain" (Box 18)
    - Unidentified: "Enoch 'n Annie", 1937 (Box 18)
      Written in tribute to Ellen Van Volkenburg.
- Theatrical Work
  - Companies and Associations
    - Adelphi Guild Theatre / Adelphi Players (England), 1943 and undated (Box 18)
    - Chicago Little Theatre (Chicago, Illinois)
      - Chicago Little Theatre articles
        - Newspaper and magazine clippings about Maurice Browne, Ellen Van Volkenburg, and the Chicago Little Theatre, 1915-1921 and undated (Box 18)
        - Printed article about the Chicago Little Theatre, 1962 (Box 18)
      - Chicago Little Theatre administrative materials
        - Chicago Little Theatre floor plan, undated (Box 18)
        - Chicago Little Theatre legal documents and meeting minutes, 1912-1917 (Box 18)
        - Chicago Little Theatre membership list, 1914 (Box 18)
        - Chicago Little Theatre Association minutes, 1914 (Box 18)
          Minutes from the Chicago Little Theatre Association's first meeting.
        - "Miscellaneous" Chicago Little Theatre materials, 1914, 1950 (Box 18)
          Includes notes on finances, lists of players, and designs (all 1914), along with Maurice Browne's explanatory notes (1950).
      - Chicago Little Theatre correspondence
        - Correspondence to the Chicago Little Theatre's secretaries (Box 18)
          Secretaries include Fanny Butcher, Facelia Hamlin, Elma Pease, and Vera White (Jonson).
        - Correspondence regarding the 1913 Chicago Little Theatre controversy (Box 18)
        - Correspondence regarding the Chicago Little Theatre lockout, 1916 (Box 18)
        - General Chicago Little Theatre correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 18)
      - Chicago Little Theatre plays and scripts
        - Calderon, George typescript: Peace, undated (Box 18)
          Includes carbon copy.
        - Materials regarding Caviare: A Revue, 1930 and undated (Box 18)
          Includes dealer description of this and other Chicago Little Theatre productions.
        - Chicago Little Theatre Passion Play
          - Chicago Little Theatre Passion Play typescript, 1913 (Box 18)
            Carbon copy. 2 copies. "A prompt copy arranged by Ellen Van Volkenburg and Maurice Browne, with a foreword by James O'Donnell Bennett." "Copy not corrected typographically."
          - Chicago Little Theatre Passion Play typescript, May 1945 (Box 18)
            Carbon copy with holograph revisions. "(Corrected, May, 1945) a prompt copy arranged by E. V. V. and M. B. ('Throwaways' and light. plot made by E. V. V. for Seattle production laid in)".
          - Chicago Little Theatre Passoin Play typescript, May 1945 (Box 18)
            Includes holograph revisions. "M. B. copy, (corrected, May, 1945) Appendix". Accompanied by a photograph.
          - Chicago Little Theatre Passion Play typescript, May 1945 (Box 18)
            "Molly's copy, uncorrected, May 1945."
        - Long, H. W. Shirley typescript: Describing Him, undated (Box 18)
          Includes carbon.
        - Morgan, Brewster manuscript: Dark Brown Taste, undated (Box 18)
          Signed holograph.
        - Sim, Alastair typescript: The Drunkard's Child, undated (Box 18)
        - The Trojan Women
          - The Trojan Woman correspondence (Box 18)
          - Maurice Browne diary on The Trojan Women American tour, 1915 (Box 18)
          - The Trojan Women tour materials, 1915 (Box 18)
            Includes correspondence, financial records, and a souvenir program.
      - Chicago Little Theatre programs and playbills
        - General Chicago Little Theatre programs and playbills, 1912-1913, 1916-1918, and undated (Box 18)
        - Fuller Sisters programs and playbills, 1913-1915 and undated (Box 18)
          Includes programs for performances at the Chicago Little Theatre and other venues.
        - Marmein, Miriam and Irene programs and playbills, undated (Box 18)
          For events at the Chicago Little Theatre.
      - Chicago Little Theatre publicity releases, ca. 1913-1918 and undated (Box 18)
        Typescirpts.
      - Chicago Little Theatre miscellany, undated (Box 18)
    - Children's Theatre Guild of (Chicago, Illinois, and Kent, England), undated (Box 19)
    - Cornish Theatre and Cornish School (Seattle, Washington)
      - Cornish Theatre and Cornish School membership materials, 1934 (Box 19)
      - Cornish School publicity materials and clippings, 1921; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Maurice Browne Ltd.
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. "Contracts, correspondence, accounts, and Captain Hill materials", 1929-1931; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. Contracts, 1930-1937
        - "Contracts connected with sundry plays of distinction", 2 folders (Box 19)
        - "Sundry London Theatre leases", 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. contracts, 4 folders (Box 19)
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. Correspondence
        - Antill, Joan M.
          - Antill, Joan M. incoming correspondence (Box 19)
          - Antill, Joan M. outgoing correspondence (Box 19)
        - Browne, Maurice outgoing correspondence, 1929-1940 (Box 19)
        - Colbourne, Maxwell incoming correspondence (Box 19)
        - Dearmer, Geoffrey incoming correspondence (Box 19)
        - Gosling, Harold
          - Gosling, Harold incoming correspondence (Box 19)
          - Gosling, Harold outgoing correspondence (Box 19)
        - Hamilton, Clifford incoming correspondence (Box 19)
        - Hill, George incoming correspondence (Box 19)
        - McLellan, Hugh incoming correspondence (Box 19)
        - Morris, Marjorie incoming correspondence (Box 19)
        - Peacey, Howard (Box 19)
        - Van Volkenburg, Ellen correspondence with Marjorie Morris, 1935-1971 (Box 19)
        - Waugh, Evelyn (Box 19)
        - Correspondence regarding Wings over Europe, 1928-1932 (Box 19)
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. "General", 1929-1932 and undated (Box 19)
        Includes financial records, correspondence, publicity materials, and clippings.
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. financial records
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. audited accounts, 1929-1936, 1938-1939 (Box 19)
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. petty cash book, January 5, 1929-October 29, 1930 (Box 19)
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. office payroll, January 26, 1929-March 22, 1930 (Box 20)
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. Sunday J. E. accounts, 1929-1930 (Box 20)
          Possibly related to Journey's End.
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. ledger, March 1930? (Box 20)
          "Seemingly during tenancy of Savoy Theatre Jan.-March 1930 (with Journey's End)."
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. Globe and Savoy Theatres cash receipts book, February 28, 1930-May 30, 1932 (Box 20)
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. expenditure record, etc., 1934-1936? (Box 20)
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. meeting minutes
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. Management Committee meeting minutes
          - Maurice Browne Ltd. Management Committee meeting minutes, December 2, 1929-January 5, 1932 (Box 20)
          - Maurice Browne Ltd. Management Committee meeting minutes, June 23, 1930-January 5, 1932; 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. Board of Directors meeting minutes, March 1929-August 1934 (Box 20)
          Includes some correspondence.
        - Maurice Browne Ltd. informal monthly meeting minutes, July 3, 1934-June 1, 1937 (Box 20)
      - Maurice Browne Ltd. plays
        - Journey's End signature books, 1929; 3 Volumes (Box 20)
        - Othello inventories, ca. 1931-1932 (Box 21)
          Folded blueprints tipped in.
        - The Venetian correspondence and schedule, ca. 1931 (Box 21)
    - Maurice Browne Theatre Association, Los Angeles
      - Maurice Browne Theatre Association materials (Box 21)
        Includes correspondence, programs, and other materials.
      - Maurice Browne Theatre Association cash book and journal, January 12, 1926-August 12, 1926 (Box 21)
      - Maurice Browne Theatre Association meeting minutes, March 1926-April 1926 (Box 21)
    - School of the Theatre, University of British Columbia, Vancouver, 1938-1939 (Box 21)
      Consists primarily of correspondence, with a small number of clippings and other materials.
    - Maurice Browne and Cecil Litchfield West End company proposal, ca. 1938 (Box 21)
  - Playbills
    - Maurice Browne and Ellen Van Volkenburg playbills
      - Maurice Browne and Ellen Van Volkenburg playbills (United States)
        - Anatol (Box 21)
        - Androcles and the Lion (Box 21)
        - Aria da Capo (see Neighbors) (Box 21)
        - Arsenic and Old Lace (Box 21)
        - Bacchae (Box 21)
        - The Bachelor (see Four Plays of Today) (Box 21)
        - Candida (Box 21)
        - The Cassilis Engagement (Box 21)
        - Catherine Parr (see Four Frankly Frivolous) (Box 21)
        - Charity That Began at Home (Box 21)
        - Cheapside (Box 21)
        - A Christmas Pantomime (see Christmastide) (Box 21)
        - Christmastide (see also Womenkind) (Box 21)
        - The Constant Lover (see Sunday Lovers) (Box 21)
        - Creditors (Box 21)
        - Deirdre of the Sorrows (Box 21)
        - Devi, Ratan and Coomaraswamy, Dr. Ananda recital and lecture (Box 21)
        - Devil's Sabbath (Box 21)
        - The Distaff Side (Box 21)
        - A Doll's House (Box 21)
        - Don (Box 21)
        - Eastward in Eden (Box 21)
        - Electra (Box 21)
        - Everybody's Husband (see King Lear's Wife) (Box 21)
        - Extreme Unction (see Four Plays of Today) (Box 21)
        - Farewell Supper (see Four Frankly Frivolous, Four One-Act Plays, and Three Fatal Dinner Parties) (Box 21)
        - The Fifth Commandment (see Womenkind) (Box 21)
        - Four Frankly Frivolous (Box 21)
        - Four One-Act Plays (Box 21)
        - Four Plays for Today (Box 21)
        - Grotesques (see Shadow Magic) (Box 21)
        - The Happy Prince (see Christmastide) (Box 21)
        - The Harlem Tragedy (see Four Plays of Today) (Box 21)
        - Hay Fever (Noel Coward) (Box 21)
        - Hedda Gabler (Box 21)
        - Hindu Gods (see Shadow Magic) (Box 21)
        - The Improper Duchess (Box 21)
        - Iphigenia in Aulis (Box 21)
        - Jael (see Sunday Lovers) (Box 21)
        - Joan of Arc (Box 21)
        - Joint Owners in Spain (see Four Frankly Frivolous, Four One-Act Plays, Creditors, and Womenkind) (Box 21)
        - Journey's End (American productions) (Box 21)
        - Kennedy-Fraser, Marjory and Patuffa, "Songs of the Hebrides" (Box 21)
        - Kindling (Box 21)
        - King Lear's Wife (Box 21)
        - The King of the Jews (Box 21)
        - Lemon Drops (see King Lear's Wife) (Box 21)
        - The Letter (see Four Plays of Today) (Box 21)
        - Litchfield-Hambourg Trio, Chicago Little Theatre (Box 21)
        - Lithuania (see Four One-Act Plays and The Pretty Sabine Woman) (Box 21)
        - The Lost Silk Hat (see Sundry Lovers) (Box 21)
        - Love in Danger (Box 21)
        - Maker of Dreams (see Four Frankly Frivolous) (Box 21)
        - The Master Builder (see also The Ship) (Box 21)
        - The Matchmaker (Box 21)
        - A Matter of Husbands (Box 21)
        - Medea (Box 21)
        - Miss Lulu Bett (Box 21)
        - Mrs. Warren's Profession (Box 21)
        - Mr. Faust (Box 21)
        - Morraca (see The Fatal Dinner Party) (Box 21)
        - The Mother of Gregory (Box 21)
        - The Mothers (see Love in Danger) (Box 21)
        - Neighbors (see also Androcles and the Lion) (Box 21)
        - On Baile's Strand (see Womenkind) (Box 21)
        - One Sunday Afternoon (Box 21)
        - Ongawa, Mr. and Michitaro, Mrs., Chicago Little Theatre (Box 21)
        - 'Op O' Me Thumb (see A Matter of Husbands) (Box 21)
        - Paolo and Francesca (Box 21)
        - The Philanderer (Box 21)
        - The Pixy (see Love in Danger) (Box 21)
        - The Possessed (Box 21)
        - Poverty Is No Crime (Alexander Ostrovsky) (Box 21)
        - Powys, John Cowper Chicago Little Theatre lectures (Box 21)
        - The Princess Who Wouldn't Say Die (Box 21)
        - The Pretty Sabine Woman (Box 21)
        - Professor's Love Story (Box 21)
        - Puppet programs (Box 21)
        - Quiet Wedding (Box 21)
        - Rosmersholm (Box 21)
        - Shadow Magic (Box 21)
        - Shall We Join the Ladies? (see The Fatal Dinner Parties) (Box 21)
        - The Ship (Box 21)
        - A Story of Pierrot (Fernand Beissier) (Box 21)
        - The Stronger (see Womenkind) (Box 21)
        - The Subjection of Kezia (see Love in Danger) (Box 21)
        - Sundry Lovers (Box 21)
        - Temperament (see King Lear's Wife) (Box 21)
        - Three Fatal Dinner Parties (Box 21)
        - Tidings Brought to Mary (see King Lear's Wife) (Box 21)
        - The Trojan Women (Box 22)
        - The Unknown Warrior (Box 22)
        - The Venetian (Box 22)
        - The Wind and the Rain (Box 22)
        - The Wizard of Oz (Box 22)
        - Womenkind, The Stronger, and Joint Owners in Spain (see also Four One-Act Plays and Four Frankly Frivolous) (Box 22)
        - Yesterday's Husband (Box 22)
        - You and I (Box 22)
      - Maurice Browne and Ellen Van Volkenburg playbills (Great Britain)
        - Alice in Wonderland (Box 22)
        - And So to Bed (Box 22)
        - As You Are (Box 22)
        - At Mrs. Beam's (Box 22)
        - B. J. One (Commander Stephen King-Hall) (Box 22)
        - The Bachelor (Box 22)
        - Badger's Green (Box 22)
        - Believe It or Not! (Box 22)
        - Beloved (André Chatellus) (Box 22)
          Adapted by Valerie Wyngate.
        - Betrayal (Box 22)
        - Bowery Touch (Box 22)
        - Bridge of Sighs (Box 22)
        - Busman's Honeymoon (Box 22)
        - Caviare (Box 22)
        - Charles and Mary (Box 22)
        - The Dance-Drama Group (Box 22)
        - The Dark Saint (Box 22)